Guide to The Boys' Club of New York Records 1876-2002 MS 3000
New-York Historical Society
- Series VII: Photographs
  - "V.I.P." photographs (Offsite-box 102, Folder 3)
  - Corporate Photographs (Offsite-box 102, Folder 4)
  - Alumni events and portraits (Offsite-box 102, Folder 5-7)
  - Alumni events (Offsite-box 103, Folder 1-2)
  - Alumni, Tompkins Square (Offsite-box 103, Folder 3)
  - Alumni, Jefferson Park -- 50th Anniversary (Offsite-box 103, Folder 4)
  - Alumni, Military Service photographs -- WWII and Vietnam (Offsite-box 103, Folder 5)
  - Annual Meetings, 1990's - 2000's (Offsite-box 103, Folder 6)
  - Women's Board Presidents (Offsite-box 103, Folder 7)
  - Women's Board, Meetings and portraits (Offsite-box 103, Folder 9)
  - Board photos, contact sheets and negatives (Offsite-box 103, Folder 10)
  - Board photos, receipts (Offsite-box 103, Folder 11)
  - Events: Testimonial Dinners (Offsite-box 104, Folder 1)
  - Events: Education Program Alumni Dinner, circa 1990's (Offsite-box 104, Folder 2)
  - Events: Tompkins Square Open House Parties, 1980's (Offsite-box 104, Folder 3)
  - Events: Harriman Clubhouse Open House, 1995 (Offsite-box 104, Folder 4)
  - Events: Various identified events, 1970's - 1990's, undated (Offsite-box 104, Folder 5)
  - Events: Unidentified (Offsite-box 104, Folder 6-8)
  - Events: Unidentified (Mary Hilliard, photographer), 2002, undated (Offsite-box 104, Folder 9)
  - Events: Unidentified (Al Levine, photographer), 1970's, undated (Offsite-box 105, Folder 1)
  - Events: Unidentified (Sam Reiss, photographer), circa 1950's - 1960's (Offsite-box 105, Folder 2)
  - Events: Unidentified (Bill Thompson, photographer), 1980's, undated (Offsite-box 105, Folder 3)
  - Events: Unidentified (Jeanne Trudeau, photographer), circa 1970's - 1980's (Offsite-box 105, Folder 4)
  - Events: Unidentified (various identified photographers), circa 1950's - 1990's (Offsite-box 105, Folder 5-6)
  - Events: Fashion shows, 1960's - 1970's (Offsite-box 105, Folder 7)
  - Events: Fashion shows, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 105, Folder 8)
  - Events: Fashion shows, 1985-1990 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 1)
  - Events: Fashion shows, 1991-1994 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 2)
  - Events: Fashion shows, 1995-1997 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 3)
  - Events: Lilly Luncheon, 2000 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 5)
  - Events: Lilly Luncheon, 2002 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 6)
  - Events: Various (photographs used in 1980's programs) (Offsite-box 106, Folder 7)
  - Events: Movie benefits, 1970's - 1980's (Offsite-box 106, Folder 8)
  - Events: Movie benefits, 1980's (Offsite-box 106, Folder 9)
  - Events: Movie benefits, 1990's (Offsite-box 106, Folder 10)
  - Events: Theater benefits, 1970's - 1980's (Offsite-box 107, Folder 1)
  - Events: Theater benefits, 1990's - 2000's (Offsite-box 107, Folder 2)
  - Events: Chocolate Bar Presentation, 21 Club, 1074 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 3)
  - Events: Antique show, 2005 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 3)
  - Events: Junior parties, 1980's (Offsite-box 107, Folder 4)
  - Events: Junior parties, 1995 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 5)
  - Events: Junior movie benefit, 1997 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 6)
  - Events: Juniors parties, 1998 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 7)
  - Events: Juniors parties, 1999 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 8)
  - Events: Juniors parties, 2000 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 9)
  - Events: Juniors parties, 2001 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 10)
  - Events: Juniors parties, 2005 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 11)
  - Events: Juniors parties?, undated (Offsite-box 107, Folder 12)
  - Events: Spa Week, Women's Board, undated (Offsite-box 108, Folder 1)
  - Events: Women's Board activities (Offsite-box 108, Folder 2)
  - Events: Golf outing, 1997 (Offsite-box 108, Folder 3)
  - Events: Antique preview (photo album) (Offsite-box 108)
  - Events: Unidentified dance (photo album), circa 2000's (Offsite-box 108)
  - Events: Spring Dance, 1960's - 1990's (Offsite-box 109, Folder 1-15)
  - Events: Spring Dance, 2000-2001 (Offsite-box 110, Folder 1-2)
  - Events: Spring Dance (photo albums), 2003, 2005 (Offsite-box 110)
  - Events: Spring Dance (photo albums), 2005 (Offsite-box 111)
  - Events: Fall Dance, 1950's - 2004 (Offsite-box 112, Folder 1-15)
  - Events: Fall Dance (photo albums), 2004, 2006 (Offsite-box 113)
  - Events: Fall Dance (photo albums), 2006 (Offsite-box 114)
  - Events: Unidentified (Fall Dance?) (Offsite-box 114, Folder 1)
  - Annual report photos, circa 1940's - 1990's (Offsite-box 115, Folder 1)
  - Publicity shots and mock-ups, circa 1940's - 1990's (Offsite-box 115, Folder 2)
  - Display photos (unframed) (Offsite-box 115, Folder 3-8)
  - Photo captions (Offsite-box 115, Folder 9)
    This folder contains captions for photographs identified with a number preceded by "BD," "CP," and "HP." Some of these photographs are in the "Display photos" folders, while others are scattered throughout the photographs arranged by subject.
    Also included in this folder are other captions that are not linked to specific photographs in the collection.
  - Correspondence regarding photographs, 1960's - 2000's (Offsite-box 115, Folder 10)
  - Photographic slides: London boxing, 1953 (Offsite-box 116, Folder 1)
  - Photographic slides: Clubhouse activities and camp, 1960's - 1970's (Offsite-box 116, Folder 2)
  - Photographic slides: Clubhouse activities, 1970's - 1980's (Offsite-box 116, Folder 3)
  - Photographic slides: Clubhouse activities/sports, 1970's (Offsite-box 116, Folder 4)
  - Photographic slides: Camp, 1970's - 1990's (Offsite-box 116, Folder 5)
  - Photographic slides: Pitt Street Clubhouse and neighborhood, 1980's, undated (Offsite-box 116, Folder 6)
  - Photographic slides: Theatrical productions, 1980, undated (Offsite-box 116, Folder 7)
  - Negatives and contact sheets, 1990's, undated (Offsite-box 117, Folder 4)
    Identified topics include clubhouse activities, baseball, swimming, education program, Christmas party, theatrical productions, buildings, and sports. There are also many unidentified negatives.
  - Negatives, 1990's, undated (Offsite-box 117, Folder 5-7)
    Identified topics include Jefferson Clubhouse, Milliken Clubhouse, Harriman Clubhouse, golf outing, camp, portraits, and sports. There are also many unidentified negatives.
  - Negatives (Offsite-box 117A)
  - Oversize photos: Buildings and street scenes (Offsite-box 118 (tall box), Folder 1-2)
  - Oversize photos: Sports and recreation (Offsite-box 118 (tall box), Folder 3-4)
  - Oversize photos: Clubhouse scenes (Offsite-box 118 (tall box), Folder 5)
  - Oversize photos: Arts and crafts (Offsite-box 118 (tall box), Folder 6-7)
  - Oversize photos: Recording studio? (Offsite-box 118 (tall box), Folder 8)
  - Oversize photos: Photo album, Camp Carey, 1918-1919 (Offsite-box 118 (tall box), Folder 9)
  - Oversize photos: Camp (Offsite-box 118 (tall box), Folder 10)
  - Oversize photos: Theater and glee club (Offsite-box 118 (tall box), Folder 11)
  - Oversize photos: Group photos, theatrical productions and band, 1907-1927 (Offsite-box 118 (tall box), Folder 12)
  - Oversize photos: Theatrical photoboards, 1940's - 1950's (Offsite-box 118 (tall box), Folder 13)
  - Oversize photos: Theatrical photoboards, 1950's - 1960's (Offsite-box 119 (tall box), Folder 1)
  - Oversize photos: Activities and portraits (Offsite-box 119 (tall box), Folder 2)
  - Oversize photos: Group photos (Offsite-box 119 (tall box), Folder 3-5)
  - Oversize photos: Portraits, Presidents (Offsite-box 119 (tall box), Folder 6)
  - Oversize photos: Events (Offsite-box 119 (tall box), Folder 7)
  - Oversize photos: New York Journal publicity shots, 1950's (Offsite-box 119 (tall box), Folder 8)
  - Oversize photos: Eliot Elisofon, photographer, 1957 (Offsite-box 119 (tall box), Folder 9)
  - Oversize photos: Dick Meek, photographer, 1961 (Offsite-box 119 (tall box), Folder 10)
  - Oversize photos: Heini Mayr, photographer, circa 1950's - 1960's (Offsite-box 119 (tall box), Folder 11-12)
  - Oversize photos: Education Program Alumni Track and Field Meet, 1995 (Offsite-box 119 (tall box), Folder 13)
  - Oversize photos: contact sheets (Offsite-box 119 (tall box), Folder 14)
  - Oversize photos: Photo of boys mounted with membership cards, circa 1950's (Offsite-box 120 (flat box), Folder 1)
  - Oversize photos: Camp Carey, 1910's - 1920's, undated (Offsite-box 120 (flat box), Folder 2)
  - Oversize photos: Group photos, 1916, undated (Offsite-box 120 (flat box), Folder 3)
  - Oversize photos: Photoboards and mounted photos of boys (Offsite-box 120 (flat box), Folder 4)
  - Oversize photos: Mock-ups (Offsite-box 120 (flat box), Folder 5-8)
  - Oversize photos: Sports photoboards, 1930's - 1950's, undated (Offsite-box 121 (flat box), Folder unknown container)
  - Oversize photos: Theatrical photoboards, 1950's - 1960's (Offsite-box 122 (flat box), Folder unknown container)
  - Oversize photos: Theatrical photoboards, 1960's - 1970's (Offsite-box 123 (flat box), Folder unknown container)
  - Oversize photos: Camp Carey photoboard, Sports and recreation photoboards, and group photograph in front of the White House, 1923-1924, undated (Oversize Small, Folder BCNY OS 2)
- Series VIII: Scrapbooks and Ephemera
  This series consists of scrapbooks and loose ephemera which provide a colorful glimpse of historical activities at BCNY.
  Scrapbooks include publicity scrapbooks (containing news clippings and advertisements relating to various benefit events); golf scrapbooks (containing news clippings relating to golf benefits); other scrapbooks of news clippings (containing clippings regarding BCNY activities and people associated with the organization); an Education Program scrapbook (containing photographic portraits of scholarship recipients and related materials); and scrapbooks from trips made by BCNY athletic teams to China (in 1999) and Cuba (in 2001).
  Loose ephemera includes postcards, programs and invitations (including many from BCNY theatrical productions), fliers, stationary, certificates, and various other "throwaway" or souvenir items. There are also objects such as athletic medals, printing blocks of BCNY logos, t-shirts, and two vinyl records. In addition, there are items created by the boys (essays and a few pieces of artwork). Items of particular interest are highlighted in the box and folder list.
  Also included in this series are information cards identifying early "club leaders" and volunteers, and early membership registers and guest books.
  - Publicity scrapbooks, 1952-1962 (Offsite-box 124)
  - Publicity scrapbooks, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 125)
  - Golf scrapbooks, 1953-1955 (Offsite-box 126)
  - Golf scrapbooks, 1956, 1958 (Offsite-box 127)
  - Scrapbook of news clippings, 1952-1956 (Offsite-box 152, Volume 39)
  - Scrapbook of news clippings, 1951-1954 (Offsite-box 152, Volume 40)
  - Scrapbook of news clippings, 1954-1957 (Offsite-box 153, Volume 41)
  - Scrapbook of news clippings, 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 153, Volume 42)
  - Scrapbook of news clippings, 1960-1968 (Offsite-box 154, Volume 43)
  - Scrapbook of news clippings, 1961-1976 (Offsite-box 154, Volume 44)
  - Scrapbook of assorted materials (includes photographs), 1940's - 1980's (Offsite-box 155, Volume 45)
  - Education Program scrapbook, 1960's - 1980's (Offsite-box 155, Volume 46)
  - Scrapbook, 1999 China Tour (includes photographs) (Offsite-box 156, Volume 47)
    Separated Materials Note
    Loose scorecards from this scrapbook have been housed with Miscellaneous ephemera in Box 129, Folder 4.
  - Scrapbook, 2001 Cuba Tour (includes photographs) (Offsite-box 156, Volume 48)
  - Early ephemera, 1905-1910, undated (Offsite-box 128, Folder 1)
    Includes early schedules of events during the tenure of Francis H. Tabor, the club's first paid professional; several programs for Gilbert & Sullivan performances by the boys; the Constitution of the Senior Club (which limits membership to "male white persons" between the ages of 18 and 24); and other early invitations and programs.
  - Letters from politicians/celebrities, 1960's - 1970's, 2005, 2007 (Offsite-box 128, Folder 2)
  - Bequest forms/stock offering, undated (Offsite-box 128, Folder 2)
  - Sports ephemera (Offsite-box 128, Folder 3)
  - Sports ephemera: Posters for London boxing match, 1953 (Oversize Medium, Folder BCNY OS 1)
    There is additional ephemera relating to the boxing matches with the London Federation of Boys in Series II, Programs and Operations, Box 26.
  - Camp ephemera, 1903-1970's (Offsite-box 128, Folder 4-6)
  - Invitations and programs, 1920's - 1990's (Offsite-box 128, Folder 7)
  - Certificates and awards, 1950's - 2000's (Offsite-box 128, Folder 8)
  - Human interest stories and boys' testimonials, 2000's (Offsite-box 128, Folder 10)
  - Fliers, 1990's, undated (Offsite-box 128, Folder 11)
  - Logos, mock-ups and patches, undated (Offsite-box 128, Folder 12)
  - Stationary and postcards (Offsite-box 128, Folder 13)
  - Artwork by BCNY members, 1997 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 1)
  - Winning essays by BCNY members, 2008-2009 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 2)
  - Boys' Club song by John Motley (sheet music), 1957 (Offsite-box 129, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous ephemera, 1930's - 2000's (Offsite-box 129, Folder 4)
    Includes itinerary of BCNY "ambassadors" for 1935 maiden voyage of French liner "Normandie" to New York, pamphlet entitled "Suggestions for Leaders," menu for Leshko's Coffee House on lower east side, BCNY business cards, and assorted other ephemera. Also includes loose scorecards of BCNY basketball games during the club's 1999 China Tour.
  - Miscellaneous ephemera (oversize), 1956, 2001, undated (Oversize Small, Folder BCNY OS 3)
    Includes promotional poster for BCNY, 80th anniversary commemoration in Spanish newspaper La Prensa, seating chart for event at the Plaza hotel, BCNY Alumni preamble, poster for benefit performance of Tosca featuring Maria Jeritza, and certificates from the Mayor and Governor of New York
  - Miscellaneous theatrical ephemera (Offsite-box 129, Folder 5)
  - Theatrical programs, Tompkins Square Playhouse productions, 1946-1960 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 1)
  - Playbills, BCNY theatrical productions, 1906-1949 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 2)
  - Playbills, BCNY theatrical productions, 1950-1952 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 3)
  - Playbills, BCNY theatrical productions, 1953-1959 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 4)
  - Playbills, BCNY theatrical productions, 1960-1966 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 5)
  - Playbills, BCNY theatrical productions, 1970-1990 (Offsite-box 130, Folder 6)
  - Playbills, BCNY theatrical productions, undated (Offsite-box 130, Folder 7)
  - Tickets, BCNY theatrical productions, 1950's - 1980's (Offsite-box 130, Folder 8)
  - Posters (Oversize Large, Oversize BCNY OS 5)
  - Information cards, BCNY Leaders, 1920's - 1950's (Offsite-box 131)
    Cards identify name and address of boy and club of which he is a leader
  - Information cards, BCNY Volunteers, 1950's - 1990's (Offsite-box 132)
  - Membership register (3 volumes), 1896- 1904 (Offsite-box 133, Folder unknown container)
  - Membership register (1 volume), 1905-1906 (Offsite-box 134, Folder unknown container)
  - Loose pages, Membership register, 1955 (Offsite-box 43A, Folder 9)
  - Guest book (1 volume), 1954 (Offsite-box 134, Folder unknown container)
  - Printing blocs, BCNY logos, undated (Offsite-box 135, Folder 1-2)
  - "I AM BCNY" bracelets, undated (Offsite-box 135, Folder 2)
  - Athletic and other award medals, 1930's - 1940's (Offsite-box 135, Folder 3)
  - William Hale Harkness medals, undated (Offsite-box 135, Folder 4)
  - Championship medals, wrestling, 1908 (Offsite-box 135, Folder 5)
  - T-shirts, Camp Northover (2), circa 1970's - 1980's (Offsite-box 136, Folder 1)
  - Vinyl records (2): "Marching Song for BCNY" and "A Christmas Eve Reading to the Children of America", undated (Offsite-box 136, Folder unknown container)
- Series IX: Digital Media
  This series includes a variety of records stored on electronic and digital media, including floppy discs, DVD's, CD's, VHS and Betamax tapes, cassette tapes, and reel-to-reel film rolls. Type of records and/or subjects include office files; benefit events; trustee, staff and alumni interviews; television segments spotlighting BCNY; films made about BCNY activities such as travel to Cuba and China; theatrical and musical performances; and films about Camp Carey in the 1930's and 1940's.
  There are also many unlabeled tapes for which the content could not be determined.
  - Board minutes, meetings, photos (12 Zip disks), 1992-2002; 187 Megabytes 12 Zip disks (887 Files, 15 Folders) (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Floppy disks are restricted from use. Patrons may request the digital files. A full file manifest is available upon request. Labels handwritten on the disks have been transcribed as the folder title.
    Disk1_Leaders; Disk2_Admin; Disk3_Minutes; Disk4_Manual; Disk5_TrusteesAndWomensBoard; Disk6_Meetings; Disk7_Photos; Disk 8_AwardsCertificatesObitsResolutions; Disk9_Minutes; Disk10_InfoJDR; Disk11_Publish; Disk12_ARPix
  - Administration, sports, photos (16 Zip disks), 1992-2005; 1 Gigabytes 16 Zip disks (2,653 Files, 85 Folders) (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Disk1_AdminBlack1; Disk2_AdminBlack2; Disk3_AdminBlack5; Disk4_AdminYellow; Disk5_PhotosGreen; Disk6_PhotosGreen2; Disk7_AdminBlue; Disk 8_PhotosBlue; Disk9_PhotosBlack1; Disk10_PhotosBlack2; Disk11_ImageAXS; Disk12_Dental; Disk13_DrsWeinAndStrife; Disk14_Meetings1997-1998; Disk15_Newsletter_09-2000; Disk16_SportsHistory
  - Correspondence, sports, annual reports (5 Zip disks, 9 3.5-inch disks), 1993-2003; 207 Megabytes 5 Zip disks and 9 3.5-inch disks (853 Files, 47 Folders) (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Disk1_B2_Correspondence; Disk2_NYDentalAcademyList2000; Disk3_McKnightOnCongelosi; Disk4_RetreatTimeline; Disk5_MasterPlan; Disk6_DollyToBrad_1; Disk7_DollyToBrad_2; Disk 8_DollyToBrad_3; Disk9_AnnualReports; Disk10_2002SPJ; Disk11_2001Sports; Disk12_AthletesData_HOFOfficials_MtgNotes_Sports_2001; Disk13_BCNYBalanceOfFiles; Disk14_1
  - Sports, journals (11 Zip disks, 8 3.5-inch disks), 1992-2003; 526 Megabytes 11 Zip disks and 8 3.5-inch disks (2,270 Files, 44 Folders) (Box 137, Folder 4)
    Disk1_SportsBios; Disk2_Sports2000-2001; Disk3_Sports97-98; Disk4_Sports1999; Disk5_SportsJournal1998; Disk6_Contribution_Holicyn_Ryan; Disk7_Admin_Sports_Spj_2001; Disk 8_Fame1-4_Aug2000; Disk9_Sports1; Disk10_Sports2; Disk11_Sports3; Disk12_SportsBlack1; Disk13_1999Journal; Disk14_BCNY_SptsJournal_1999; Disk15_BCNY99Journal; Disk16_SptsJournal[Illegible]; Disk17_NoLabel; Disk18_Journal1994-2000; Disk19_BCNY_Text_1999
  - List and index of files on office files floppy discs (Box 137, Folder 5-8)
  - Women's Board, fundraising events, meeting minutes (3 CDs, 14 3.5-inch disks), 1994-2007; 415 Megabytes 3 CDs and 14 3.5-inch disks (573 Files, 17 Folders) (Box 137, Folder 9)
    CD1_InternshipPictures; CD2_ISPPhotosForJournal_20070419; CD3_BCNY_ATC; Disk1_Marquis; Disk2_Minutes_ColorVersion_19970114; Disk3_JrPartyFall2001_Thea2002; Disk4_FallAttendees_1993-2000; Disk5_JrSummerParty1999_March2000JrBenefit; Disk6_CapJulAttendees1993-94_Movie1995-99; Disk7_[NoLabel]; Disk8_SpaDay98; Disk9_FashionAttendees1993-2000; Disk10_SpringAttendees1994-2000; Disk11_[NoLabel]; Disk12_PressRelease_SportsHamiltonGroup_OpenHouse_2002; Disk13_[NoLabel]; Disk14_[NoLabel]
  - Trustee, staff and alumni Interviews/oral histories/radio segments/financial (34 Cassettes, 5 Micro Cassettes, 1 5.25 inch floppy disc) (RESTRICTED), 1980's -1990's (Offsite-box 138)
  - Unlabeled tapes (16 VHS tapes) (RESTRICTED), undated (Offsite-box 138)
  - Tapes about BCNY: "Cuba Chronicle" (3 tapes), "Beijing Diary" (3 tapes), "Crossroads Italy" (1 tape), "The Island School" (1 tape), "Friends for Life" (3 tapes), "BCNY" by Dennis Powers Productions, Long Version (3 tapes), Short Version (2 tapes), "BCNY Faces" (1 tape), "Building Better Boys" (2 tapes), Brad Zervas Orientation for New Prep Students (1 tape) [20 VHS/BMS/DVD tapes total] (RESTRICTED), 1990's - 2000's (Offsite-box 139)
  - Clubhouse events (4 VHS tapes -- Christmas, Thanksgiving, etc.), Camp Cromwell (2 VHS tapes), "Showtapes" (2 VHS tapes)[8 VHS tapes total] (RESTRICTED), 1990's - 2000's (Offsite-box 139)
  - Benefits: All-Sports Hall of Fame Dinners and Theater Benefit (27 VHS/BMS/DVD tapes) (RESTRICTED), 1980's - 2000's (Offsite-box 140)
  - Fundraising appeals (13 VHS/DVD tapes) (RESTRICTED), 1990's - 2000's (Offsite-box 140)
  - Commercial [non-BCNY] films (3 VHS tapes - shown at clubhouse?) (RESTRICTED)
  - Alumni events (2 tapes), Dedication dinners and ceremonies (8 tapes/discs), Ron Robinson Basketball highlights (1 tape) [11 VHS/DVD tapes total) (RESTRICTED), 1980's - 2000's (Offsite-box 141)
  - Television segments and promotional tapes (24 VHS/DVD/CD tapes) (RESTRICTED), 1980's - 2000's (Offsite-box 141)
  - Theatrical and musical performances (43 VHS/DVD/CD/cassette tapes) (RESTRICTED), 1970's - 2000's (Offsite-box 142)
  - Theatrical performances, BCNY interviews (16 reel tapes) (RESTRICTED), 1970's - 1980's (Offsite-box 143)
  - Camp Carey, Boxing in London, AFL/CIO, promotional films about BCNY and other unlabeled films (37 film rolls) (RESTRICTED) (Offsite-box 144)
  - Camp Carey, Yogi Bear Promotion, "Story of the Pilgrims" (4 film rolls) (RESTRICTED) (Offsite-box 145)
  - "Old Glory: History of the U.S. Flag" plus two unlabeled film rolls (3 film rolls in total) (RESTRICTED) (Offsite-box 146)
  - Camp Carey, Sports Reel, plus one unlabeled film roll (3 film rolls in total) (RESTRICTED), 1951, 1956, undated (Box 147 (tall box))